we help financial advisory businesses scale.
On average right now, we're doing about 45K a month.
Problem?
I'm the main point of failure.
Can you get customers easily right now?
Yeah.
Okay, so getting customers is not a problem.
So the issue is delivering for the customers.
Yeah, like I haven't lost any clients,
but if I were to double it right now,
I would start not being able to service clients.
Step one is you need to think in workflows rather than roles.
Almost all asset creation has become incredibly commoditized.
Like you're building out those flows,
which when a new customer comes in,
that should kick off a process that then spins up VSL,
spins up ads, spins up creative.
So how many hours a day you spend building it?
Oh, it's all of my time right now.
The bad news is that you don't have any real problems
with your business.
You know what your constraint is, which is delivery.
The next constraint that's gonna come up
is gonna be sales.
Plug them into the AI and then ask for the recurring themes
that people say their problems are before they buy.
Take that list of problems, reintegrate that into the VSL.
We did this and it literally doubled our acquisition.
We literally just took only the pain points
that people said, put those in, and then we're like,
we literally made a document called Why People Buy.